(Bernadette:)Well, there are a couple of
opportunities available,
(Bernadette:)but I volunteered for the
premature ejaculation project.
(Bernadette:)I mean, it's not like either
one of us has heart disease.
(Bernadette:)Oh, I almost forgot.
I got you a little present.
(Howard:)Oh, Bernie, no.
You didn't have to.
(Bernadette:)I wanted to.
Come on, open it.
(Howard:)You bought me a Rolex?
(Howard:)How much did this cost?
(Bernadette:)Oh, you let me worry
about the money.
(Bernadette:)I just want my baby
to have pretty things.
(Raj:)More wine?
(Penny:)Oh, no, no, no. I've had
way too much already.
(Sheldon:)Here's an interesting
fact about alcohol...
(Penny:)Hit me.
(Sheldon:)Man is not the only species